CHU, FANG-YI

+07477863158 imfangchu@gmail.com https://fangchu.github.io/works/

As a UI/UX designer with 6years industry experience focus on creativity website and visual design in the highest quality and coding W3C. solve design problems with user-centred design techniques.

ACHIEVEMENT

· #Struggles(book) nominated for best cover design in Taiwan.

This book has sold more than 2,000 copies in Taiwan. https://www.books.com.tw/products/0010734823

* "The Life of Homeless Dog" project published by a Wuo-Wuo Magazine.

Wo Bao Bao is the only magazine in Taiwan that combines design to illustrate issues with animals and raise awareness about endangered species. I cooperated with Wuo-Wuo as a commissioned illustrator and created visuals for the magazine. The magazine is now popular and well-known in Taiwan.

National College Student Research Scholarship from Ministry of Science and Technology in Taiwan.

I produced and designed an Augumented reality eco-education project. It was experimented at Yong Long Primary School and it received good feedback from the students. The project was later awarded the Scholarship from the Ministry of Education.

Skills

Tools Sketc, Zeplin, Adobe Creative Suite, Invision, Storyboard, Balsamiq, Paper, Slack.

Programing Html, Css/Sass, Pug/Jade, Jquery, Javascript, Boostrap, Npm, Gulp, Git, Github.

Work Experience

Freelance

Designer London UK · 2019 - present

- · Responsible for visual on the official website and planning the design guideline independently for Non-profit organizations.
- Developed websites including visual design and front-end programming.

Rakuya .Inc (Rental Websites)

UI/UX Designer OCT. 2014 ~JULY.2018



- Set standards for wireframes and user fows, created prototypes for user testing.

 Presented competitor analysis, usability research and design solutions to executive team as an essential
- Redesign and implement the sell/rent objects websites with the team, replacing the old website structure with a new one, improved user experience on devices and upgraded users' visit rate from 20% to 70%.
- Responsible for UI design of web & mobile apps for website and networking system.
- Extensive experience building responsive websites utilising HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.
- Communicate and collaborate with the development team and marketing team to ensure that designs are delivered as per the brief and acceptance criteria specified.

Grazingcat Design Studio



Web Designer OCT. 2013 ~JULY.2014

- Design the UI, and interaction flow of new web and mobile applications.
- Designed startups' web and mobile apps including strategies, interaction design and visual design and received high ratings on customer satisfaction survey.
- Responsible for planning and developing e-newsletters and operating facebook media while bringing the most popular articles to the newsletter.
- Implement different projects with the team. I took part in at least 20 website projects, my roles in Coding (Joomla, HTML/CSS) and Visual Design for websites.
- · Experience collaborating with developers and tech teams.

ECI.SOFT

Web Designer OCT. 2011 ~SEP.2013

- Collected and organized the requirements from customers for supporting decision.
- · Built UI flow and wireframe and prototypes.

EDUCATION

Asia University , Taiwan (2006 - 2011)

Bachelor of Arts degree in Department of Digital Media Design GPA 82.47 Subjects | Animate and Web design.

HOBBIES

- · table tennies
- movies
- · mobile game

LANGUAGES

- · Mandarin (native)
- English (intermediate)